It's great to be in the Empire today
We got everything
(Raj:)Try to keep up, Howard. I'm killing it.
(Howard:)Yeah, I wish we looked as cool
dancing in clubs as we do right now.
(Leonard:)Don't worry, this is exactly how you look
when you're dancing in clubs.
(Raj:)You're welcome, ladies.
(Sheldon:)Paradigm-shifting news, gentlemen.
Dude, I was about
to Bollywood this bitch.
(Sheldon:)Earlier today, I invited
Professor Stephen Hawking to join me...
(Sheldon:)...in the popular online game
"Words With Friends."
(Sheldon:)Moments ago, he accepted my request.
Do you understand what that means?
(Howard:)That somewhere, right now,
Stephen Hawking is saying:
"Damn it. I meant to click 'no'."